And this is why it's so dangerous and insidious.
It is a complete constitutional gaslight.
And it is meant to essentially empty out the victories of the civil rights movement.
And Amanda, if I would say one thing, I think it's so important for us to get this piece.
Understand that everything they are doing, we have been so successful.
By successful, I don't mean we've solved, you know, racism or anything like that.
But I mean, we have been moving at such a determined and brisk pace.
Mm-hmm.
That they are, they feel they have no choice but to run the tables at this moment, to turn back the clock.
What you just described about the Freedom Fund is that there are enough successful Black people in place to reach back.
Right.
This is what scares them.
Thank you.